曾经在某地 有位拥有神奇力量的和尚
他所画的画就像有生命一般 能自由活动
人们都觉得毛骨悚然
和尚越来越难以跟别人相处
于是他就孤身一人 安静地躲在山中过日子
古都 黑兔回忆录
I think of how it all was made
我思考着这一切是如何被创造的
Each detail of this world portrayed
描写了这世界每一个细节
In bursts of color, every sight and sound
连接出现的无数色彩 一切的景象和声音
The wide blue sky and the immobile ground
还有广阔的蓝天与稳固的大地
It's all too great to understand
这一切伟大得让人难以理解
The moon, with one stroke of his hand
在他着下一笔后
Started to glow and all the stars appeared
明月开始发出光亮 并出现众多繁星
How did it all end up here
这奇迹究竟如何产生
I am here at this crucial time
我在关键时刻来到此处
Hope I find what I came to find
希望我能找到我来找寻的
I'm destined to be, the way I'm meant to be
这是注定好的 也是必须发生的
I have to find my way
我一定要找到我路
This is the secret of my life
这是我一生的秘密
Learn to love and always seek for what is right
学懂去爱 与永能找出正确的事
And learn all things change, some flowers die while others grow
与了解世上的所有变化 有些花会枯萎但也有花顺利成长
Some gifts are only seen, not held
而某些事物只能可见 却无法拥有
There are lots of things I still don't know
还有很多事情是我无法知晓
I feel your gentle smile sometimes
我有时能感觉到你温柔的笑容
But know I can't go back in time
但要知道我是无法回到过去
I won't fight even all these lonely tears
我甚至不会压抑所有寂寞的泪水
Cause they allow me to be close to you
因为它们令我更加亲近你
Summer turns cold, red leaves fly by
夏天结束天气转凉 红叶落下开始起舞
Seasons change but they don't ask why
四季转变 但它们不问原因
All part of this maze, long nights before the dawn
所有都在迷阵中 黎明前的漫漫长夜
And I have your song
而我有你的歌声
This is the secret of my life
这是我一生的秘密
Learn to love and always seek for what is right
学懂去爱 与永能找出正确的事
And learn all things change, some flowers die while others grow
与了解世上的所有变化 有些花会枯萎但也有花顺利成长
Some gifts are only seen, not held
而某些事物只能见得 无法拥有
Seldom understood, but felt
能理解的不多 但能感受到
乖乖 别哭哦
我们肯定会再见的
说好了
I know that you must think of me
我知道你定会想起我
So you are never far
所以你永远不会远离我
I can be where you are
我能知道你在何方
This is the secret of my life
这是我一生的秘密
Learn to love and always seek for what is right
学懂去爱 与永能找出正确的事
All life must change, just like water falls and turns to clouds again
所有生命都必须改变 就像雨点从天落下后又能转化为白云
Some gifts are lost and some return
会丢失某些事物 某些又会归来
There are lots of things I still must learn
还有太多事情是我需要去学习
SGS曙光社字幕组制作
歌词：solosodium贤伉俪、Kangaroo、红姐姐贤伉俪、诸位美国友人
这就结束了?
这个啊 谁知道呢